Levi Magnus

Coldstream, British Columbia, Canada levi.magnus@alumni.ubc.ca 250-938-4519

OVERVIEW

I am a fourth year Bachelor of Science student specializing in Computer Science at the University of British Columbia's Okanagan campus. Strong communication and organizational skills, as well as previous experience working on a vast array of projects, will help me excel at your company.

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia, Kelowna, BC

Bachelor of Science – Major in Computer Science, Minor in Data Science Academic Average – 85.4%

2015 - Present Expected June, 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Computer Science, UBC (Kelowna, BC) Mobile Application Developer in Assistive Technologies

September, 2019 - Present

- Sole developer of an augmented reality guidance application intended to assist senior citizens with mild cognitive impairment in completing tasks
- The application is being built using Unity and the C# programming language and is intended for use with Android mobile devices and head-mounted displays (Microsoft HoloLens)
- Agile development methodology is being used
- User testing conducted with a group of seniors and data is being gathered for a research paper

UBC Okanagan Centre for Teaching and Learning (Kelowna, BC) Learning Technologies Rover

January, 2019 - May, 2019

- Supported faculty and staff in the use of various technologies that enhance teaching and learning
- Solved issues that arose with any of the learning technologies on campus
- Helped faculty design engaging online courses including custom course pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

UBC Centre for Teaching, Learning and Technology (Vancouver, BC)

May, 2018 - December, 2018

Canvas Technology Rover

- Assisted the UBC campuses with the transition to the Canvas learning management system
- Redesigned the UBC Canvas support website to meet W3C standards and improve the user experience, resulting
 in increased traffic to the site and positive user feedback
- Worked with the UBC Canvas API User Community to develop, test, document and maintain Python scripts that added to existing Canvas functionality and integrated the platform with other tools used at UBC
- Provided Canvas support and training to faculty and staff in the form of written documentation, one-on-one consultations, and workshop presentations

Church of God of Prophecy – Western Canada (Vernon, BC) Web Designer

February, 2017 - April, 2017

- Worked closely with the clientele to gather the requirements for the website and plan out the design
- Customized the structure and appearance of the website using HTML and CSS
- Used a content management system (WordPress) as the backend so the clientele could easily update the site

AWARDS